<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SensorRecord</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="no_sensor_error">You can\'t use SensorRecord on this device because you don\'t have any of the required sensors.</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_text"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Documentation</h1>
        This page explains how to use SensorRecord.
        <h2>Recording sensor data</h2>
        <i>Please follow the instructions below.</i>
        <ul>
            <li>Set a fitting title for your trip, so that it\'s easier to find later</li>
            <li>Press <b>Start recording</b> when you are seated in the aircraft</li>
            <li>Press <b>Add marker</b> for each of these events:\n
                <ul>
                    <li>Pushback (the aircraft leaves the gate)</li>
                    <li>Taxi (the aircraft starts driving toward the runway using its own engines. This happens after the aircraft has been stationary for a short while after pushback)</li>
                    <li>Takeoff (when the aircraft is on the runway and you hear the engines increase power, i.e., not when the aircraft lifts off, but when it starts accelerating)</li>
                    <li>Landing (the second the aircraft touches the ground again)</li>
                    <li>Park (when the aircraft stops at the gate)</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>Press <b>Stop recording</b> when you exit the aircraft\n</li>
        </ul>


        <b>Add marker</b> opens a dialog requesting a title and a confirmation (OK/Cancel). The timestamp is saved when <b>Add marker</b> is pressed, not when <b>OK</b> is pressed.
        Therefore, please press <b>Add marker</b> at the exact moment one of the listed events happen (takeoff, landing, etc.).

        <br><br>

        The app runs in the background, so you don\'t need to have it open except when you\'re adding a marker. It also displays a notification while running that, if pressed, opens the app for you.

        <br><br>

        Have a nice trip!

        <h2>After your trip</h2>
        <i>Depending on the length of your recording, processing the data might take up to a minute. Please be patient.</i>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the navigation drawer of the app by pressing the hamburger menu button in the <b>top left corner</b></li>
            <li>Select <b>History</b></li>
            <li>Click on your recording (listed as <i>your_title.zip</i>)</li>
            <li>Use your preferred platform to share the file</li>
        </ul>

        <br>

        <b>Thank you!</b>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="set_title">Please set a title</string>
    <string-array name="markers">
        <item>Pushback</item>
        <item>Taxi</item>
        <item>Takeoff</item>
        <item>Landing</item>
        <item>Park</item>
        <item>Custom</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>